<helpDefinition>
  <title>EC-WebLogic - Help</title>
  <componentContainer>
    <LINK REL="StyleSheet" HREF="../../plugins/EC-WebLogic/pluginhelp.css" TYPE="text/css" MEDIA="screen"/>
    <div class="help" >
    
    <h1 class="help">EC-WebLogic</h1>

    <h2 class="help">Overview</h2>
        <p class="help">
        This plugin allows users to interact with the Oracle WebLogic server and accomplish tasks such as starting and deploying applications, starting managed servers, and running Jython scripts.
        </p>
    <p class="help">
            <b>Supported WebLogic version</b><br/>
            This plugin was developed and tested with WebLogic version 11g (10.3.4).
       </p>

    <h2 class="help">Configuration</h2>
     <p class="help">
               To enable Commander to communicate with your WebLogic server, create a WebLogic configuration, supplying the following information:
	</p>
          <ul>
          <li><b>Configuration Name</b> - Provide a unique name for the configuration, keeping in mind that you may need to create additional configurations over time.</li>
          <li><b>URL</b> - Provide the URL for the WebLogic server, it must include the protocol and port (example: t3://localhost:7001).</li>
          <li><b>Credential</b> - Provide the username and password for the WebLogic Admin Server.</li>
          </ul>
          
     <h2 class="help">Using the Plugin</h2>
          <p class="help">
	  	    See the <a href="/commander/link/showHelp?page=plugins&amp;section=using">Commander online help system</a> for details about how to use this plugin within a procedure.
	  	    </p>
	  	    
	  	    <p class="help">
	  	    When you provide information for this plugin, fill-in the fields as follows:
	    </p>

          <p class="help">
          The StartManagedServer subprocedure starts a specified managed server instance on the selected resource machine. Required credentials must be stored
          securely in a boot.properties file.
          StartManagedServer has the following fields:
          </p>
          <ul>
               <li><b>configname</b> - Provide the name of the configuration that holds connection information for the WebLogic server.</li>
               <li><b>instancename</b> - Provide the name of the instance to start.</li>
               <li><b>scriptlocation</b> - Provide the absolute path to the start server script. It must include the filename and extension.</li>
               <li><b>wlstabspath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the wlst executable. It must include the filename and extension.</li>
          </ul>

          <p class="help">
          The StartAdminServer subprocedure starts a specified admin server instance on the selected resource machine.
          StartAdminServer has the following fields:
          </p>
          <ul>
               <li><b>configname</b> - Provide the name of the configuration that holds connection information for the WebLogic server.</li>
               <li><b>admininstancename</b> - Provide the Admin Server instance name to start.</li>
               <li><b>wlstabspath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the wlst executable. It must include the filename and extension.</li>
               <li><b>scriptlocation</b> - Provide the absolute path to the start server script. It must include the filename and extension.</li>
          </ul>

          <p class="help">
          The StopManagedServer subprocedure stops a specified managed server on the selected resource.
          StopManagedServer has the following fields:
          <ul>
               <li><b>instancename</b> - Provide the name of the instance to stop.</li>
               <li><b>scriptlocation</b> - Provide the absolute path to the stop server script. It must include the filename and extension.</li>
          </ul>
          </p>
          
          <p class="help">
          The StopAdminServer subprocedure stops a specified Admin Server instance on the selected resource.
          StopAdminServer has the following fields:
          <ul>
               <li><b>scriptlocation</b> - Provide the absolute path to the stop server script. It must include the filename and extension.</li>
          </ul>
          </p>          
          <p class="help">
          The CheckServerStatus subprocedure checks the status of the specified server.

          CheckServerStatus has the following fields:
          </p><ul>
               <li><b>configname</b> - Provide the name of the configuration that holds connection information for the WebLogic server. In this case, only credentials are taken from the configuration.</li>
               <li><b>instancename</b> - Indicate the name of the server instance to check.</li>
               <li><b>maxelapsedtime</b> - Define the maximum time in seconds that the job will try to check into the server. Blank implies no wait time (server only checked once).</li>
               <li><b>successcriteria</b> - Indicate the expected correct result to be obtained, either <b>Server running</b> or <b>Server not running</b>. If the indicated success criteria matches the returned result, it is considered successful, otherwise the step fails.</li>
               <li><b>wlstabspath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the wlst executable. It must include the filename and extension.</li>
          </ul>
          
          <p class="help">
          The CheckPageStatus subprocedure checks the status of the specified page,
          by getting the returned HTTP code from the URL.
          </p><ul>
               
               <li><b>configname</b> - Provide the name of the configuration that holds connection information for the WebLogic server.</li>
               <li><b>maxelapsedtime</b> - Indicate the maximum allowed time to check the status of a page.</li>
               <li><b>successcriteria</b> - Indicate the status of the page that must be matched, either 
                a <b>Page found</b> or a <b>Page not found</b> status. If the indicated success criteria matches the
                returned status at the end of the analysis, it is considered successful. Otherwise, it is an error in the job.  
               </li>
               <li><b>targeturl</b> - Provide the URL of the page to check.</li>
          </ul>
          
          <p class="help">
          The RunWLST subprocedure runs Jython scripts on the server.
          RunWLST has the following fields:
          </p><ul>
               <li><b>wlstpath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the wlst executable. It must include the filename and extension.</li>
               <li><b>scriptfilepath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the Jython script to execute with WLST.</li>
               <li><b>additionalcommands</b> - Provide any additional parameters for WLST.</li>
               <li><b>scriptfilesource</b> - Indicate the source of the script file. <b>Supplied file</b> uses the file whose path is indicated in the <b>scriptfilepath</b> parameter and executes it. <b>New Script File</b> indicates that a script file with the content of the <b>scriptfile</b> parameter will be executed.</li>
               <li><b>scriptfile</b> - Provide the content of the script file to execute if <b>New Script File</b> is selected in the <b>scriptfilesource</b> parameter.</li>
          </ul>
          
          <p class="help">
          The StartApp subprocedure is starts an application on the server.
          StartApp has the following fields:
          </p><ul>
              <li><b>javaparams</b> - Provide any Java options to add to the process.</li>
              <li><b>javapath</b> - Provide the absolute Java location to use. The filename is required. The default is java.</li>
              <li><b>appname</b> - Provide the name of the application to start.</li>
              <li><b>configname</b> - Provide the name of the configuration that holds connection information for the WebLogic server.</li>
              <li><b>additionalcommands</b> - Provide any additional parameters for weblogic.Deployer.</li>
              <li><b>envscriptpath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the setDomainEnv script, including the filename and extension.</li>               
          </ul>
          
          <p class="help">
          The StopApp subprocedure is stops an application on the server.
          StopApp has the following fields:
          </p><ul>
              <li><b>javaparams</b> - Provide any Java options to add to the process.</li>
	      <li><b>javapath</b> - Provide the absolute Java location to use. The filename is required. The default is java.</li>
	      <li><b>appname</b> - Provide the name of the application to stop.</li>
	      <li><b>configname</b> - Provide the name of the configuration that holds connection information for the WebLogic server.</li>
	      <li><b>additionalcommands</b> - Provide any additional parameters for weblogic.Deployer.</li>
              <li><b>envscriptpath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the setDomainEnv script, including the filename and extension.</li> 
              <li><b>gracefulmode</b> - If checked, this enables stopping the application in graceful mode.</li>
           </ul>
          
          <p class="help">
          The DeployApp subprocedure deploys an application on the server.
          The following fields are available for DeployApp:
          </p><ul>
                 <li><b>javaparams</b> - Provide any Java options to add to the process.</li>
		<li><b>javapath</b> - Provide the absolute Java location to use. The filename is required. The default is java.</li>
	      <li><b>appname</b> - Provide the name of the application to deploy.</li>
                 <li><b>apppath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the archive to deploy, including the filename and extension.</li>
                 <li><b>configname</b> - Provide the name of the configuration that holds connection information for the WebLogic server.</li>
	      <li><b>additionalcommands</b> - Provide any additional parameters for weblogic.Deployer.</li>
                 <li><b>targets</b> - Provide the targets on which to deploy the application or module.</li>
                 <li><b>envscriptpath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the setDomainEnv script, including the filename and extension.</li>
                
              </ul>
          
          <p class="help">
          The UndeployApp subprocedure undeploys an application on the server.
          UndeployApp has the following fields:
          </p><ul>
		<li><b>javaparams</b> - Provide any Java options to add to the process.</li>
		<li><b>javapath</b> - Provide the absolute Java location to use. The filename is required. The default is java.</li>
		<li><b>appname</b> - Provide the name of the application to undeploy.</li>
                 <li><b>apppath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the archive to undeploy, including the filename and extension.</li>                 
                 <li><b>configname</b> - Provide the name of the configuration that holds connection information for the WebLogic server.</li>
	      <li><b>additionalcommands</b> - Provide any additional parameters for weblogic.Deployer.</li>
                 <li><b>envscriptpath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the setDomainEnv script, including the filename and extension.</li>
                 <li><b>gracefulmode</b> - If checked, this enables undeploying the application in graceful mode.</li>
           </ul>
           
           <p class="help">
          The RunDeployer subprocedure runs weblogic.Deployer in a free-mode, specifying the command and parameters.
          RunDeployer has the following fields:
          </p>
          <ul>
              
              <li><b>commandtouse</b> - Indicate the command to pass to weblogic.Deployer (Cancel, Deploy, Distribute, Listapps, List, Listtask, Redeploy, Start, Stop, Undeploy, Update).</li>
              <li><b>javaparams</b> - Provide any Java options to add to the process.</li>
              <li><b>javapath</b> - Provide the absolute Java location to use. The filename is required. The default is java.</li>
              <li><b>appname</b> - Provide the name of the application to manage.</li>
              <li><b>configname</b> - Provide the name of the configuration that holds connection information for the WebLogic server.</li>
              <li><b>additionalcommands</b> - Provide any additional parameters for weblogic.Deployer.</li>
              <li><b>envscriptpath</b> - Provide the absolute path to the setDomainEnv script, including the filename and extension.</li>               
           </ul>
           
           
     
               
     <h2 class="help">Additional Information</h2>
          <ul>
               <li><a href="http://www.oracle.com/us/products/middleware/application-server/weblogic-suite/index.html">WebLogic home page</a></li>
               <li><a href="http://download.oracle.com/docs/cd/E17904_01/web.1111/e13702/wldeployer.htm#i1006569" target="_blank">weblogic.Deployer reference</a></li>
          </ul>
        
    <h2 class="help">Release Notes</h2>
    
        <h3 class="help">EC-WebLogic-1.1.0.0</h3>
        <p class="help">
        <ul>
             <li>Added the CheckPageStatus procedure</li>
             <li>Modified the CheckServerProcedure procedure, CURL is not needed and parameters were changed</li>
             <li>Fixed minor bugs</li>
             <li>Removed CURL dependency </li>
             <li>Added new postp matchers </li>
        </ul>
        </p>
        
        <h3 class="help">EC-WebLogic-1.0.2.0</h3>
        <p class="help">
        <ul>
             <li>Fixed minor bug on Configuration List page.</li>
             
        </ul>
        </p>
        
        <h3 class="help">EC-WebLogic-1.0.1.0</h3>
        <p class="help">
        <ul>
             <li>Procedures have one step only and are executed using Perl directly</li>
             <li>Credentials in the StartManagedServer procedure must be stored in a boot.properties file</li>
             
        </ul>
        </p>
        
     </div>
  </componentContainer>
</helpDefinition>
